(Amy:)Ready for the
aquarium?
(Sheldon:)I am. You know, and in an effort
to reduce awkwardness
(Sheldon:)as we learn how to function as friends,
I printed out a list
(Sheldon:)of safe topics
for polite conversation.
(Amy:)If that makes you
more comfortable.
(Sheldon:)If there were a list of things
that make me more comfortable,
(Sheldon:)lists would be
on the top of that list.
(Sheldon:)Okay, now... Oh.
"Since last we spoke,
have you acquired any pets?"
(Amy:)No. You?
(Howard:)No.
Um, "Since last we spoke,
have you planned
or gone on any vacations?"
(Amy:)I might go visit my aunt
next week.
(Sheldon:)Mm. Your aunt
in Modesto?
(Amy:)No, the one in
Bakersfield.
(Sheldon:)Bakersfield. I see.
(Sheldon:)Where has this list been
all my life?
(Soup Kitchen Manager:)We're gonna have you
washing dishes.
(Soup Kitchen Manager:)Uh, aprons and rubber gloves
are here... just...
(Soup Kitchen Manager:)scrape, wash and stack.
(Soup Kitchen Manager:)If you need me, I'll be around.
(Howard:)So we don't even get to be up front
where the action is?